(Mrs Wolowitz:)Oh!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)I had a pastrami
sandwich.
(Mrs Wolowitz:)She had eggplant lasagna.
(Mrs Wolowitz:)Like that's what a person
orders in a Jewish deli.
(Howard:)Besides food, did you get along?
Did you talk?
Oh, sure! Did you know
she's going to school
(Mrs Wolowitz:)to become a
microbiologist?!
(Howard:)No, she never mentioned it.
(Mrs Wolowitz:)I bet she did and
you didn't listen!
(Howard:)Yeah, that's probably it.
So, what do you think?
(Howard:)Do you like her?
She's great, huh?
She's a lovely girl!
Cute as a button!
(Howard:)That's good to hear,
'cause I've got some news.
(Mrs Wolowitz:)I hope it's
good news,
(Mrs Wolowitz:)because I've got nothing but
disappointment in here!
(Howard:)Bernadette and I
are getting married.